{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian3.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "un giorno"
            ],
            "answer": "una giornata",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516903111.9064343,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a day\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E anche sono uno studente",
                "E anche, io sono uno studente"
            ],
            "answer": "E anche io sono uno studente.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903045.0313354,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And me, too, I'm a student.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un pomeriggio",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903069.5479097,
            "question": "Given the definition \"an afternoon\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Il Signore Belli e' un uomo",
                "Il signore Belli e' un uomo"
            ],
            "answer": "Il signor Belli e' un uomo.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903025.183889,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mr. Belli is a man.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lui e' un poliziotto"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui e' un poliziotto.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903117.8987944,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He's a policeman.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una televisione",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903087.319305,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a television\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un giorno",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903103.7390754,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a day\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una stazione",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903061.6351607,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a station\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco una famiglia"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco una famiglia.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903145.7429414,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is a family.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei e' una professoressa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e' una professoressa.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903141.2871678,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She's a teacher.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il ragazzo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903132.974802,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the boy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Il signore Belli e' il padre"
            ],
            "answer": "Il signor Belli e' il padre.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903174.7546146,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mr. Belli is the father.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E io ho una sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "E ho una sorella.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903164.3478034,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And I have a sister.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a day",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903148.7749128,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una giornata\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco la famiglia Belli"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco la famiglia Belli.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903128.1666863,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here is the Belli family.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un signore",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903177.4747908,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a gentleman\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e' il fratello",
                "C'e il fratello"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il fratello.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903195.6703384,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the brother.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the son"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the son.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903240.0941966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il figlio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lei e' una studentessa",
                "Lei e' una studentessa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e' una studentessa.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903245.9742873,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She's a student.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the baby boy"
            ],
            "answer": "the boy child",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903212.570632,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il bambino\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the daughter"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the daughter.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903183.694726,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la figlia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are the brother and the sister"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the brother and the sister.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903218.714896,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il fratello e la sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e la sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la sorella.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903225.4463236,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the sister.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is a family"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is a family.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903231.9426694,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco una famiglia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a day",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903286.8938441,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un giorno\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a gentleman",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903290.950019,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un signore\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Francesco e' un ragazzo"
            ],
            "answer": "Francesco e' un ragazzo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903279.2418745,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Francesco is a boy.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Francesco e' il figlio"
            ],
            "answer": "Francesco e' il figlio.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903258.0897567,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Francesco is the son.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la persona",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516903294.7982612,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the person\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io ho un padre"
            ],
            "answer": "Ho un padre.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903284.6901097,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have a father.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un ragazzo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903250.9625878,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a boy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E io ho una madre"
            ],
            "answer": "E ho una madre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903263.3783228,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And I have a mother.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the mother"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the mother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903330.7458565,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the sister",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903312.6263463,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la sorella\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "there is"
            ],
            "answer": "There is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903306.9582074,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are the son and daughter",
                "There are the son and the daughter"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the son and the daughter.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903322.0577073,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il figlio e la figlia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "La signora Belli e' la madre"
            ],
            "answer": "La signora Belli e' la madre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903304.5821342,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mrs. Belli is the mother.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are"
            ],
            "answer": "There are...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903324.6659591,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ci sono"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903327.0259373,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are...\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un uomo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903309.6788654,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a man\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I have a father"
            ],
            "answer": "I have a father.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903345.5418108,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ho un padre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il padre e la madre"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il padre e la madre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903368.920932,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the father and the mother.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the person",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903333.9458199,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la persona\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la famiglia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903349.4381926,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the family\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mrs. Belli is the mother"
            ],
            "answer": "Mrs. Belli is the mother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903360.486002,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La signora Belli e' la madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a doctor"
            ],
            "answer": "a male doctor",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903342.7978978,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un dottore\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a television",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903352.2136712,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una televisione\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la figlia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903340.069601,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the daughter\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the family",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903404.6694393,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la famiglia\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a baby girl"
            ],
            "answer": "a girl child",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903402.2613878,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una bambina\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the daughter",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903376.1060567,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la figlia\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria e' una ragazza"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria e' una ragazza.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516903410.341945,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Maria is a girl.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a boy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903371.4735975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un ragazzo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il figlio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903380.1768827,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the son\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a station",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903383.2416945,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una stazione\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the brother"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the brother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903398.2374625,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il fratello.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il bambino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903415.8528996,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the boy child\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il fratello e la sorella"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il fratello e la sorella.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903450.5809064,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the brother and the sister.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il fratello",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903430.577302,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the brother\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the mother",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903422.065601,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la madre\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un dottore",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903435.081706,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a male doctor\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is a teacher"
            ],
            "answer": "She's a teacher.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903419.3174303,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei e' una professoressa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am Italian"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm Italian.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903438.040737,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono italiano.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e'...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903440.865103,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is...\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una ragazza",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903453.7891023,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a girl\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I have a small family",
                "I hae a small family"
            ],
            "answer": "I have a small family.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903467.489338,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io ho una famiglia piccola.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una bambina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903489.9430838,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a girl child\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria is the daughter"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria is the daughter.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903485.0338516,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Maria e' la figlia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is a student"
            ],
            "answer": "She's a student.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903502.8598511,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei e' una studentessa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e la figlia"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la figlia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903462.5468137,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the daughter.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "He is a policeman"
            ],
            "answer": "He's a policeman.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903494.6045663,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui e' un poliziotto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "La signora Belli e' una donna",
                "Il signora Belli e' una donna"
            ],
            "answer": "La signora Belli e' una donna.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903479.877148,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mrs. Belli is a woman.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io ho una famiglia piccola",
                "Ho una famiglia piccola"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ho una famiglia piccola.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903510.9745839,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have a small family.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Francesco is a boy"
            ],
            "answer": "Francesco is a boy.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903531.4061005,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Francesco e' un ragazzo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the father",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903537.650922,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il padre\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la sorella",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903535.4441197,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the sister\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is the family Belli"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is the Belli family.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903526.8174925,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco la famiglia Belli.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a girl",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903543.3831246,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una ragazza\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono il figlio e la figlia"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono il figlio e la figlia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903522.3696012,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are the son and the daughter.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la madre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903540.4013767,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the mother\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mrs. Belli is a woman"
            ],
            "answer": "Mrs. Belli is a woman.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903558.3381522,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La signora Belli e' una donna.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Francesco is the son"
            ],
            "answer": "Francesco is the son.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903553.285532,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Francesco e' il figlio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "an afternoon",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903573.434044,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un pomeriggio\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "an evening",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903569.6122367,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una sera\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e' la madre",
                "C'e la madre"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' la madre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903566.9183352,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the mother.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the father"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the father.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903561.9047587,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' il padre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mr. Belli is a man"
            ],
            "answer": "Mr. Belli is a man.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903548.5329285,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il signor Belli e' un uomo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And I have a mother",
                "I have a mother"
            ],
            "answer": "And I have a mother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903579.5385993,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E ho una madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono Francesco"
            ],
            "answer": "Io sono Francesco.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903583.5841086,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'm Francesco.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the brother",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903587.1738272,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il fratello\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the son",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903622.9561183,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il figlio\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "THere are the father and mother",
                "There are the father and the mother"
            ],
            "answer": "There are the father and the mother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903611.4837525,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono il padre e la madre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is the sister"
            ],
            "answer": "There's the sister.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903590.6519787,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' la sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria e' la figlia"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria e' la figlia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903620.5103343,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Maria is the daughter.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And I to am a student",
                "And also I am a student"
            ],
            "answer": "And me, too, I'm a student.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903602.723808,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E anche io sono uno studente.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a baby boy"
            ],
            "answer": "a boy child",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903625.8831987,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un bambino\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a woman",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903648.3460531,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una donna\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un bambino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903633.8346412,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a boy child\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the boy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903642.6617362,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il ragazzo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria is a girl"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria is a girl.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903638.088292,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Maria e' una ragazza.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a man",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903640.4382794,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un uomo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am Francesco"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm Francesco.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903629.7964928,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io sono Francesco.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una donna",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903645.9871132,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a woman\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e il figlio"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il figlio.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903653.0952132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the son.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono Italiano"
            ],
            "answer": "Sono italiano.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903675.7416625,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'm Italian.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "And I have a sister"
            ],
            "answer": "And I have a sister.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903671.5762649,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E ho una sorella.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una sera",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903667.4268017,
            "question": "Given the definition \"an evening\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e il padre"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' il padre.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903680.4185739,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There's the father.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il padre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903655.5822167,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the father\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mr. Belli is the father"
            ],
            "answer": "Mr. Belli is the father.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516903662.981266,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il signor Belli e' il padre.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        }
    ]
}